metin2sg.com 2011-03-17

# Metin 2 SG - Free to play action MMORPG

TEC Interactive ("TEC Interactive," "we," "us") is concerned about online privacy issues and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose your Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below). This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") describes our practices in connection with Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through our web sites located at http://www.metin2.sg and the Metin2SG game service (collectively, the "Site"). This Policy does not address our practices regarding information that we collect by any other means, other than through the Site; nor does this Policy govern the collection, use or disclosure of information by any of our affiliates (collectively, "Affiliated Entities") or by third parties. 

By using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time by posting the new Policy on the Site. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by referring to the "LAST UPDATED" legend at the top of this page. Any changes to our Policy will become effective upon our posting of the revised Policy on the Site. Use of the Site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Policy then in effect. This terms and conditions of this Policy are incorporated into the Metin2SG End User License Agreement. By clicking on the checkbox in the Metin2SG registration form, you consent to the collection and processing (including the disclosure and international transfer) of personally identifiable information about you as described in the Privacy Policy. 

1\. What Types of Information Does TEC Interactive Collect From Me? 

TEC Interactive gathers three basic types of information through the Site: "Personally Identifiable Information" (or "PII"), "Non-Personally Identifiable Information" (or "Non-PII") and ?IP Addresses?. Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies you as an individual. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is aggregated information, demographic information and any other information that does not reveal your specific identity. An IP Address is the Internet Protocol address of the computer that you are using. 

a. Personally Identifiable Information. You do not have to provide PII to use the Site. However, in order for you to take advantage of particular opportunities provided through the Site (for example, to access certain areas and services on the Site, such as the message boards and newsletters), we may require that you furnish PII. We collect PII from you through the Site, such as your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number or other payment account number, only when you voluntarily provide it to us. 

b. Non-Personally Identifiable Information. When you visit and interact with the Site, TEC Interactive and third parties with whom TEC Interactive has contracted to provide services to TEC Interactive may collect Non-PII. Non-PII is generally collected through the Site from four different sources: environmental variables, cookies, pixel tags and other similar technologies and information that you voluntarily provide. 

i. Environmental Variables. We and our service providers may collect certain environmental variables, such as your MAC address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, OS version, Internet browser, and Internet browser version. These environmental variables are collected by most browsers, and can be used to optimize your experience on the Site. 

ii. Cookies. We and our service providers may use ?cookies? on the Site. Cookies are data that a web server transfers to an individual's computer for recordkeeping purposes. We use cookies and other technologies to better serve with more tailored information and facilitate your ongoing access to and use of our Site. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of a particular cookie, or cookies from a particular web site, to your computer. To learn more about cookies, please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. 

iii. Pixel Tags. We and our service providers may also use so-called "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags") in connection with some Site pages and HTML-formatted e-mail messages to, among other things, compile aggregate statistics about Site usage and response rates. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1x1), that is ordinarily not visible to Site visitors and may be associated with Cookies on the visitors? hard drives. Pixel Tags allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Site, to deliver branded services, and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. When used in HTML-formatted e-mail messages, Pixel Tags can tell the sender whether and when the e-mail has been opened. 

iv. Information That You Voluntarily Provide. TEC Interactive also collects Non-PII when you voluntarily provide such information to us. When such information is not combined with any PII, such information is considered to be Non-PII, as it does not personally identify you or any other user. Additionally, we may aggregate PII in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of the Site, for example, by using PII to calculate the percentage of users who live in a particular region. Such aggregate information is considered Non-PII for purposes of this Policy. 

c. IP Addresses. When you visit and interact with the Site, TEC Interactive and third parties with whom TEC Interactive has contracted to provide services to TEC Interactive may collect IP Addresses. Your Internet Protocol (?IP?) address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Site Provider (?ISP?). This number is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you visit the Site, along with the date(s) and time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) that you visited. 

2\. How Does TEC Interactive Use Information Collected From Me? 

a. Personally Identifiable Information. We may use PII about you in the following ways: 

i. Fulfillment of Requests. TEC Interactive may use PII about you to fulfill the purpose for which such PII was provided (e.g., to send product information to you or fulfill your purchase). 

ii. Administrative Communications. From time to time, in our sole discretion, we may use PII about you to send to you important information regarding the Site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies or other administrative information. Because this information may be important to your use of the Site, you may not opt-out of receiving such communications. 

iii. Other Communications. We may use PII about you to inform you of products, programs, services, special deals, promotions and newsletters that we believe may be of interest to you; provided that you ?Opt-In? to receive this information. 

iv. Purchases. When you make a purchase through the Site, we may collect your credit card number or other payment account number, billing address and other information related to such purchase (collectively, "Payment Information") from you, and may use such Payment Information in order to fulfill your purchase. 

v. Electronic Postcards and Other Messages to Friends. We may provide functionality to permit you to send messages regarding Site-related content to a friend through the Site. For example, we may offer ?Send to a Friend? promotions, like electronic postcards on our Site or through our newsletters. If you wish to use this feature, you may provide us with your friend?s e-mail address and the name of your friend, so that we can facilitate your sending of such message to your friend. We do not use your friend?s PII for any other purpose other than the express purpose given in connection with such functionality, unless otherwise disclosed to you at the time you provide such PII to us. 

vi. Promotions. We may operate sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions (collectively, "Promotions") through the Site. We typically ask you for certain PII when you enter and, if applicable, win a Promotion. You should carefully review the rules, if any, of each Promotion in which you participate through the Site, as they may contain additional important information about TEC Interactive' use of PII about you. To the extent that the terms and conditions of such rules concerning the treatment of PII about you conflict with this Policy, the terms and conditions of such rules shall control. 

vii. Internal Business Purposes. We may also use PII about you for our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits and so forth. 

b. Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Because Non-PII does not personally identify you, we may use such information for any purpose. In addition, we reserve the right to share such Non PII, which does not personally identify you, with Affiliated Entities and other third parties, for any purpose. In some instances, we may combine Non-PII with PII (such as embedding e-mail addresses in cookies). If we do combine any Non-PII with PII, the combined information will be treated by us as PII hereunder as long as it is so combined (see Section 2(a) above). 

c. IP Addresses. We use your IP address, and the IP addresses of all users, for all purposes listed in Section 2(a), as well as for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, providing better service to users of the Site, customizing the Site based on your preferences, compiling and analyzing statistics and trends, and otherwise administering and improving the Site for your use. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice on the Internet and is done automatically by many web sites. Please note that we treat IP Addresses, server log files and related information as Non-PII, unless required to do otherwise under applicable law. 

3\. How Is Personally Identifiable Information Disclosed? 

a. Third-Party Service Providers. We work with third parties who provide services which may include, but not limited to, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment and other services of an administrative nature. We reserve the right to share PII about you with such third parties for the purpose of enabling these third parties to provide such services (for example, if you choose to make a purchase through the Site, we may share your Payment Information or other PII with our third-party service providers to fulfill your purchase, including, without limitation, to process your credit card or payment account number). 

b. Affiliate Communications. We may share PII about you with the Affiliated Entities to allow them to contact you regarding products, programs, services and promotions that they believe may be of interest to you; provided that you ?Opt-In? to allowing Affiliated Entities to contact you. 

c. Third-Party Communications. We may share PII about you with third parties to allow them to contact you regarding products, programs, services and promotions that they believe may be of interest to you; provided that you ?Opt-In? to allowing such third parties to contact you. 

d. Promotions. We reserve the right to share the PII you provide in connection with Promotions with third party sponsors of such Promotions (regardless of whether such Promotions are hosted by us), or otherwise in accordance with the rules applicable to such Promotion. You should carefully review the rules, if any, of each Promotion in which you participate through the Site, as they may contain additional important information about a sponsor's or other third parties? use of PII about you. To the extent that the terms and conditions of such rules concerning the treatment of PII about you conflict with this Policy, the terms and conditions of such rules shall control. 

e. Profiles. We may provide functionality on the Site that allows you to create a ?profile page? (your ?Profile?) and post certain information and materials on your Profile. Please note that your Profile, including all PII available in your Profile, may be accessible to other users. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose PII about you, or any other information, in your Profile. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF ANY PII YOU DISCLOSE IN YOUR PROFILE. 

f. Forums and Message Boards. As a service to our users, TEC Interactive may offer message boards, blogs, online discussions and other public forums (each a ?Forum") where users with similar interests can share information, post questions and comments. You may be required to register and choose a user name and password to access a Forum. Please note that any information (including PII) that you reveal in a Forum is publicly viewable on the Site. We urge you to exercise discretion and think carefully before disclosing any PII or any other information in any Forum. What you have written and posted to the Forum may be seen, disclosed to or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict, including to contact you for unauthorized purposes. In particular, as your user name will be visible to the public in any Forum, we advise you not to use your real name as your user name. As with any public forum on any site, this information may also appear in third-party search engines. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE OF ANY PII YOU VOLUNTARILY DISCLOSE THROUGH A FORUM. 

g. Electronic Postcards and Other Messages to Friends. Please note that any PII you provide in connection with sending messages regarding Site-related content to a friend through the Site, such as your name and your e-mail address, will, of course, be disclosed to your friend. 

h. Assignment. We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from Site users to an Affiliated Entity or a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of TEC Interactive' business, assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). 

i. Law Enforcement; Emergencies; Compliance. Notwithstanding any other provision of this Policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose PII about you to others as we believe to be appropriate (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to governmental requests; (d) to enforce our Terms of Service; (e) to protect our operations or those of any Affiliated Entities; (f) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of TEC Interactive, the Affiliated Entities, you or others; and (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. For example, we may, to the fullest extent the law allows, disclose PII about you to law enforcement agencies to assist them in identifying individuals who have been or may be engaged in unlawful activities. 

4\. Other Important Notices Regarding Our Privacy Practices. 

a. Children?s Privacy. The Site is not directed toward individuals under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any PII online from individuals under the age of 13. Our Terms of Use prohibit individuals under the age of 13 from registering or otherwise participating in our Site. 

b. Third-Party Sites. The Site may contain links to third-party web sites. These linked sites (including without limitation the web sites of Affiliated Entities) are not under TEC Interactive' control and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of any such linked site, or any link contained in any linked site. We provide such links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by TEC Interactive or any Affiliated Entities. If you provide any PII through any such third-party web site, your transaction will occur on such third party's web site (not the Site) and the PII you provide will be collected by, and controlled by the privacy policy of, that third party. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and practices of any such third parties. PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS POLICY DOES NOT ADDRESS THE PRIVACY OR INFORMATION PRACTICES OF ANY THIRD PARTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE AFFILIATED ENTITIES. 

c. Third-Party Advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. Please note that these companies may use information (not including PII) about your visit to this Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp. 

d. Security. We seek to have security measures and tools, such as firewalls, in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, although we strive to protect PII about you, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through or in connection with the Site or that is stored by us. You acknowledge and agree that any information you transmit through the Site or upload for storage in connection with the Site is so transmitted or stored at your own risk. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with Section 4.j ("Contacting Us") below (note that if you choose to notify us via physical mail, this will delay the time it takes for us to respond to the problem). 

other than to the email or physical addresses specified in this paragraph. 

f. Changing or Updating PII. If you would like to review, correct, or update the PII about you that has been previously provided to us through the Site, you may access your PII through the ?My Account? link at the top of the Site. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes, and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. Finally, we are not responsible for removing or suppressing information from the databases of third parties with whom we have already shared PII about you, or limiting their use of PII about you. 

g. Retention Period. We will retain PII about you for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy unless a longer retention period is required by law and/or regulations. 

h. Jurisdictional Issues. TEC Interactive does not represent or warrant that the Site, or any part thereof, is appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Site do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit the Site's availability, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion. By using the Site and submitting any PII, you consent to the transfer of PII to other countries, such as the United States, which may provide a different level of data security than in your country of residence. 

i. Contacting Us. If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or any problems arise, please contact us by e-mail at info@tec-interactive.com . Please note that e-mail communications will not necessarily be secure; accordingly you should not include credit card information or other sensitive information in your e-mail correspondence with us. 

If you have any questions or comments, kindly contact TEC Interactive at the following address: 

ATTN: Privacy Policy Enquiries 

TEC Interactive 

Ubi Techpark 

10 Ubi Crescent #02-70 Singapore 408564 

Tel: 6749 7493 Fax: 6749 9945
